const questions = [
    {
      id: 1,
      question: "What does 'History' refer to?",
      options: ["Future plans", "Mathematics", "Study of past events", "Cooking style"],
      correctAnswer: "Study of past events",
      marks: 2
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: "What is the study of ancient societies called?",
      options: ["Zoology", "Archaeology", "Geology", "Sociology"],
      correctAnswer: "Archaeology",
      marks: 2
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      question: "What is 'Polyandry'?",
      options: ["Multiple wives", "Multiple husbands", "No marriage", "Single marriage"],
      correctAnswer: "Multiple husbands",
      marks: 2
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      question: "What does 'Illegible' mean?",
      options: ["Understandable", "Not readable", "Visible", "Transparent"],
      correctAnswer: "Not readable",
      marks: 2
    },
    {
      id: 5,
      question: "What does 'Opaque' mean?",
      options: ["See-through", "Not see-through", "Transparent", "Invisible"],
      correctAnswer: "Not see-through",
      marks: 2
    },
    {
      id: 6,
      question: "What is a 'Legislature'?",
      options: ["A court", "Government body for making laws", "Military unit", "Police agency"],
      correctAnswer: "Government body for making laws",
      marks: 2
    },
    {
      id: 7,
      question: "What does 'Aristocracy' mean?",
      options: ["Government by the poor", "Government by the people", "Government by the nobles", "No government"],
      correctAnswer: "Government by the nobles",
      marks: 2
    },
    {
      id: 8,
      question: "What does 'Incredible' mean?",
      options: ["Believable", "Not believable", "Understandable", "Normal"],
      correctAnswer: "Not believable",
      marks: 2
    },
    {
      id: 9,
      question: "What does 'Invisible' mean?",
      options: ["Can be seen", "Not able to be seen", "Very big", "See-through"],
      correctAnswer: "Not able to be seen",
      marks: 2
    },
    {
      id: 10,
      question: "What is 'Contraband'?",
      options: ["Legal items", "Taxed goods", "Prohibited by law to import/export", "Certified products"],
      correctAnswer: "Prohibited by law to import/export",
      marks: 2
    },
    {
      id: 11,
      question: "Who is called 'Venerable'?",
      options: ["Very old", "Respected for wisdom", "Aggressive", "Talkative"],
      correctAnswer: "Respected for wisdom",
      marks: 2
    },
    {
      id: 12,
      question: "What is an 'Outrider'?",
      options: ["A biker", "A person escorting another in a vehicle", "A soldier", "A guard"],
      correctAnswer: "A person escorting another in a vehicle",
      marks: 2
    },
    
  ];
  

  
  export default questions;
  